Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts, 1928-1958
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- 16mm As-Broadcast Microfilm, 1928-1958
  - Ward Baking
    - Tennessee Jed, 1946 Jan.-Aug.
    - Tennessee Jed, 1946 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 313)
      [Missing Aug. 20; no broadcast Aug. 21-22]
    - Tennessee Jed, auditions, 1946 Nov.-Dec.
  - General Cigar (White Owl)
    - Yankees baseball, 1946 Mar.-July
    - Yankees baseball, 1946 July-Sept. (Reel 314)
  - J.B. Williams
    - CBS News, Wm. L. Shirer, commercials, 1946
    - CBS News, KFH, WINR, WHP, WGBF, commercials, 1946 Sept.-Dec.
    - CBS News, WTIC, commercials, 1946
  - Shell Oil (Reel 341)
    - Shell Show, 1934 Jan.-1935 Mar.
      [California Office; missing Jan. 22, 29, Feb. 5, 12, 1934]
    - Shell Show, 1935 Mar.-Apr. (Reel 342)
      [California Office]
  - Edgar Bergen
    - Pictures and press notices, 1937-1939
  - Cream of Wheat
    - Alexander Woollcott, Town Crier, 1935 Oct. 6
      [California Office; see reel 7 for more]
  - Emerson Drug Co. (Bromo-Seltzer)
    - Grenlund and His Girls, 1935 Aug. 20
      [California Office; see reel 244 for more]
    - Harriet Parsons, 1938 Jan.-Mar.
      [California Office; missing Jan. 12]
  - Standard Brands
    - Fleischmann's, Royal, Rudy Vallee, 1938-1939
    - In the Dark, S. Eilers and N. Eddy, 1937 Oct. 3
    - Mr. Jonas Changes His Mind, Edward Arnold, 1938 July 29
  - London
    - Current list of radio programs in London, 1937
      [London Office]
  - Horlick's
    - Horlick's Picture Show, 1937-1938
      [London Office; programs 163-164]
  - Standard Brands (Reel 343)
    - Tenderleaf Tea, Tommy Dorsey, 1945 June 10
      [California Office; see reel 279 for rest]
    - Royal Gelatin, auditions, Bertrice Lillie, 1945
    - Tenderleaf Tea, One Man's Family, undated
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1934 Nov.
      [California Office; see reel 103 for more]
    - Lux Radio Theatre, The Men Without a Country, 1934 Feb. 22
    - Lux Toilet Soap Movie Club, 1938
      [London Office; programs 41-59]
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Music Hall, 1936 June
      [California Office; see reel 122 for more]
    - Bing Crosby, pictures and press notices, circa 1933
    - Kraft Miracle Whip, article, 1933
    - Speech by Gen. G.S. Patton, Jr., 1942 Oct. 28
    - Parkay margarine, The Great Gildersleeve, 1941 Sept.-Oct.
    - Commercials, 1942 Jan.-June
    - Kraft Mayonnaise, commercials, 1942 Jan.-June
    - Sealtest, National Dairy Association, Rudy Vallee, 1942-1943
      [California Office; Includes photograph of Vallee's dummy Sally Ann]
    - Sealtest, National Dairy Association, Sealtest Village Store Program, Jack Haley, Dennis Day, 1943 July-Nov.
    - Sealtest, National Dairy Association, commercials, 1942 May.-1943 Dec.
  - Old Gold Cigarettes (Lorillard)
    - Herbert Marshall, 1942 Apr. 24
      [California Office; see reel 209 for more]
  - Nash Motors
    - Grace Moore and Vincent Lopez, 1937 May-June
  - Safeway Stores
    - Commercials, 1942
  - Weco Products
    - Dr. West Celebrity Night, 1936 Apr.-May
  - General Cigar (White Owl)
    - Burns & Allen, 1931-1933
  - Textron
    - Textron Theatre, Helen Hayes. 1946 Jan.-Mar.
  - Libby, McNeil & Libby (Reel 354)
    - My True Story, 1947
      [Starts with episode 708]
    - My True Story, 1947 June-Oct. (Reel 355)
      [Starts with episode 823]
    - My True Story, 1947 Oct.-Nov. (Reel 356)
      [Starts with episode 918]
    - Monitor Reports, 1946 Jan.-Apr.
    - My True Story, 1946 Apr.-Aug., Oct. (Reel 357)
      [Starts with episode 513; continued from reel 346]
    - My True Story, 1946 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 358)
      [Starts with episode 608; see reel 360 for Aug. 14 and first 5 pages of aug. 15 broadcasts]
  - Standard Brands (Reel 359)
    - One Man's Family, 1947
      [See reel 361 for Feb. 9 broadcast]
    - Commercials, 1947 Jan.-Nov.
  - Libby, McNeil & Libby (Reel 360)
    - My True Story, 1946 aug. 14-15
  - Standard Brands
    - One Man's Family, 1947
    - Commercials, 1947 Nov.-Dec.
    - Fred Allen Show, 1947
    - Commercials, 1947
    - Chase & Sanborn, commercials, 1947
  - Brillo Manufacturing Company
    - Commercials, 1947 Jan.-Apr., Oct.-1948 Jan.
  - Mentholatum
    - Commercials, 1947 Nov.
  - Owens Illinois Glass Co.
    - Commercials, 1947 July-Sept.
  - Penick & Ford
    - Br'er Rabbit, commercials, 1947 Sept.-Dec.
  - E.R. Squibb
    - Commercials, 1947 June-Dec.
  - Standard Brands (Reel 361)
    - Chase & Sanborn, Edgar Bergen, 1947 Jan.-May, Sept.-Dec.
    - Chase & Sanborn, Alex Templeton, 1947 June-Aug.
  - Parker Pen
    - Information Please, commercials, 1947 Jan.-June
      [No broadcast Mar. 5]
  - U.S. Government, Citizens Food Committee
    - Who's for Who in America, special broadcast, 1947 Nov. 18
  - International Police
    - Jitters in Geneva (by Welbourn Kelley), audition, 1945 Sept. 29
  - Seven-Up
    - Seven-Up Show, Barney Grant, audition, 1945 Feb. 6
  - General Cigar (White Owl)
    - Quentin Reynolds and Bennett Cerf, audition, 1945 May 7
  - J.B. Williams
    - Eddie Mayehoff Looks at the News, audition, 1947 Apr. 1
  - Standard Brands
    - One Man's Family, 1947 Feb. 9
      [See reels 359-360 for rest of year]
  - Ford Motor Company
    - The Ford Show, Dinah Shore, 1947 Jan.-Mar.
    - The Ford Show, Dinah Shore, 1947 Apr.-June (Reel 362)
    - Commercials, 1947
  - Johns-Manville
    - Bill Henry News, 1947
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    - Music America Loves Best, 1947
      [Missing Oct. 19]
  - Planter's Peanuts
    - Commercials, WTIC, 1947 Jan.-July
    - Commercials, WTIC, 1947 Aug.-Oct. (Reel 363)
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Music Hall
      - Eddy Duchin, 1947 Jan.-June
      - Nelson Eddy, 1947 July-Sept.
      - Al Jolson, 1947 Oct.-Dec.
      - Kraft Television Theatre, 1947 May 7-June 25
        [Through second act of June 25, I Like It Here]
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1947 June 25-Nov. 12 (Reel 364)
      [Through second act of Nov. 12, Ladies in Retirement]
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1947 Nov. 12-Dec. (Reel 365)
      [From third act of Nov. 12, Ladies in Retirement]
  - Standard Brands
    - Television shows
      - Face to Face, 1947 Jan.
      - Hour Glass, 1947 Jan.-Mar.
      - Dancing on Air, 1947 Feb.-Mar.
  - J.B. Williams
    - William L. Shirer News, 1947 Jan.-Mar.
    - Commercials, 1947 Jan.-Aug.
  - P. Ballantine & Sons
    - Commercials, 1947
    - Scott & Grauer television show, 1947 Oct.-Dec.
    - Dinty's 3-Ring Sports Dugout, 1947 Aug.-1948 Jan.
    - Yankee Baseball, 1947 Mar.-May
    - Yankee Baseball, 1947 May-Sept. (Reel 366)
    - Yankee Football, 1947 Oct.-Dec.
  - Fannie Farmer Candies
    - Commercials, 1947
  - P. Ballantine & Sons
    - Commercials, baseball, 1947 Apr.
  - General Cigar (White Owl)
    - International Cigar, 1945 Oct. 24
    - Yankee Baseball, commercials, 1947 Apr.-July
    - Yankee Baseball, commercials, 1947 July-Sept. (Reel 367)
    - White Owl Sports Smoker, 1947 Oct.-Dec.
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1947 Jan.-June, Aug.-Sept.
      [Through second act of Sept. 15, The Seventh Veil]
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1947 Sept. 15-Dec. (Reel 368)
      [From third act of Sept. 15, The Seventh Veil]
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, CBS Biography, 1949 Feb. 11
  - Ward Baking
    - Tennessee Jed, 1947 Jan.-May
    - Tennessee Jed, 1947 May-Nov. (Reel 369)
    - Commercials, WAPI, Birmingham, Ala., 1946-1948 July
    - Commercials, WPDQ, Jacksonville, Fla., 1946 Oct.-1947 Jan.
    - Commercials, WPDQ, Jacksonville, Fla., 1947 Feb.-1948 July (Reel 370)
    - Commercials, WJAX, Jacksonville, Fla., 1946 Feb.-1948 July
    - Commercials, WNEW, New York, N.Y., 1948 Jan.-July
    - Commercials, WNLC, New London, Conn., 1946-1948 July
    - Commercials, WNAC. Boston, Mass., 1948 Mar.-July
    - Commercials, WAGE, Syracuse, N.Y., 1947 July-1948 July
    - Commercials, WSBC, Chicago, Ill., 1945 Dec.-1948 July
    - Commercials, WSGN, Birmingham, Ala., 1948 Jan.-July
    - Commercials, WSBT, South Bend, Ind., 1946-1948 July
    - Commercials, WHK, Cleveland, Oh., 1948 Jan.-July
    - Commercials, KQV, Pittsburg, Pa., 1948 Jan.-June
    - Commercials, KSO, St. Louis, Mo., 1948 Jan.-July
    - Commercials, WHFC, The Bohemian Hour, 1948 Spring
    - Commercials, H-E-P recorded spots, 1946 Dec.-1947 Jan.
    - Commercials, WWNY, Watertown, N.Y., 1945 Nov.-1948 July
    - Commercials, WSUN, 1947 July-1948 July
    - Commercials, WXYZ, Detroit, Mich., 1948 Jan.-July
    - Commercials, WLEU, Erie, Pa., 1948 Jan.-May
    - Commercials, WLEU, Erie, Pa., 1947-1948 (Reel 371)
      [Includes spots for Florida announcement, Aunt Hannah's Kiddie Show]
    - Commercials, WJAX, Jacksonville, Fla., 1946-1948 Mar.
      [Tip Top Tunes, new programming]
    - Commercials, WALT, music program, 1948 June-July
    - Commercials, WDEV, Waterbury, Vt., 1946-1948 July
      [Tip Top Musical Almanac]
    - Commercials, WCAO, Baltimore, Md., 1948 Jan.-June
    - Commercials, WCAO, Baltimore, Md., 1948 July (Reel 372)
    - Commercials, WBAL, Baltimore, Md., 1946 Nov.-1948 July
    - Commercials, WCBS, New York, N.Y., 1947 Apr.-1948 July
      [The Missus Goes A-Shopping]
    - Commercials, WEAN, Providence, R.I., 1948 Jan.-July
      [Tello-Test]
    - Commercials, WEEI, Boston, Mass., 1948 Feb.-July
      [Breakfast in Boston]
    - Commercials, WEEI, Boston, Mass., 1948 Jan.-July
      [Top 'o the Morning]
    - Commercials, WEEI, Boston, Mass., 1947 July-1948 Mar.
    - Commercials, WHKC, Columbus, Oh., 1947 May-1948 July
      [15 minute news]
    - Commercials, WGN, Chicago, Ill., 1947 June-1948 July
      [Musical Clock, Record, Reveille]
    - Commercials, WFBR, Baltimore, Md., 1947 June-1948 July
    - Commercials, WFLA, Tampa, Fla., 1947 June-1948 July
    - Commercials, WGES, Chicago, Ill., 1946-1947 July
      [Polish Dinner Bell]
  - Lever Brothers (Reel 416)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1948
      [No broadcast June 21]
    - Aunt Jenny Hitchhikes, 1948 Aug.-Dec.
  - Western Union
    - Auditions, Easter telegrams, 1948 Mar.
    - Auditions, Mother's Day, 1948 Apr.
  - Women's National Republican Club, 1947 Sept., 1948 Sept.-Oct. (Reel 417)
  - United Churches Canvass
    - One Man's Family, History in Words and Pictures, 1935
    - One Man's Family, 1948 Jan.-May
    - One Man's Family, 1948 June-Aug.
    - One Man's Family, 1948 Sept.-Dec. (Reel 418)
    - Royal Baking Powder, 1937 June 29
    - Royal desserts, 1937 July 1
    - Fleischmann's yeast for bread, 1938 June 29
    - Edgar Bergen Show, 1948 Jan.-May, Oct.-Dec.
      [No broadcast Apr. 11; Dec. 19 broadcast missing]
    - Commercials, 1948
    - Royal Pudding, Desserts, Robert Shaw Chorale, 1948 June-Sept.
  - Brillo Manufacturing Company
    - Polly the Shopper, commercials, 1948 Jan.-Feb.
  - Libby, McNeil & Libby
    - Commercials, 1948
  - Swift & Co.
    - Salesmen conference, commercials, 1948 Apr. 8
  - Penick & Ford
    - Br'er Rabbit, commercials, 1948 Jan.-May
  - R.T. French
    - Instant Potatoes, commercials, 1947 May-1948 Apr.
  - J.B. Williams
    - Glider, commercials, 1948 Jan.-June
  - Fannie Farmer Candies
    - Commercials, 1947 Sept.-Dec.
    - Commercials, 1948 Jan.-Sept. (Reel 419)
  - Eastman Kodak
    - Commercials, 1947 Jan.-Sept.
  - Elgin Watch
    - Thanksgiving Show, 1948 Nov.25
    - Christmas Show, 1948 Dec. 25
  - Ford Dealers of America
    - Fred Allen Show, 1948 Jan.-June, Oct.-Dec.
  - Ford Motor Company
    - Calypso, 1947 July-Aug.
    - Lincoln-Mercury, 1947 Dec.
    - Trucks, 1947 Dec.
    - Commercials, 1948 Mar.-May
    - Import sales,1948 Oct. 11
    - Television shows, Dodger baseball, commercials, 1948
    - Television shows, auditions, 1948 Mar. 19
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    - Television, 1948 Nov.-Dec.
    - Spot announcements, 1948 Mar. 18
    - Music America Loves Best, 1948 Jan.-June
    - Music America Loves Best, 1948 June-Dec. (Reel 420)
  - Johns-Manville
    - Bill Henry News, 1947 Dec.-1948 Apr.
    - Bill Henry News, 1948 May-Dec. (Reel 421)
      [No broadcasts June 21-Aug. 20]
  - Emerson Drug Co. (Bromo-Seltzer)
    - Commercials, 1935 Apr.-May
    - Commercials, Tom Howard, 1936 Jan.
    - Commercials, Tito Guiza, 1936 Feb.-Mar.
    - Commercials, 1938 Jan.-June
    - Commercials, Canada, E. Maloney writer, undated
    - Commercials, Canada, Let's Disagree, 1939 Oct.-1940 Mar.
    - Commercials, Robert Shaw Chorale, 1948 Sept.-Dec.
  - Ward Baking
    - Aunt Hannah's Bread, commercials, 1948
    - Recorded spots, Tip Top Bread, 1947 Jan., 1948 Jan.
    - Advox commercials, Tip Top Bread, jingles, 1948 Dec. 14
    - Bread and cake, spot announcements, 1948 Feb.-July, 1948 Jan.
    - Spot announcements, 1948 Jan.-July (Reel 422)
    - Participation spots, 1948 Jan.-July
  - General Cigar (White Owl)
    - White Owl Sports Smoker, 1948 Jan.-Apr.
      [See also reel 423]
    - Yankee Baseball, 1948 Mar.-Sept.
  - P. Ballantine & Sons
    - Recorded spots, 1947 Sept., 1948 Apr.
    - Dinty's 3-Ring Sports Dugout, commercials, 1948 Jan.-May
    - Yankee Baseball, 1948 Mar.-June
    - Yankee Baseball, commercials, 1948 June-Oct.
  - General Cigar (White Owl)
    - Yankees baseball, 1948 Sept.-Oct.
  - P. Ballantine & Sons
    - Yankee Baseball, 1948 Apr.-Sept.
    - Scott & Grauer television show, 1948
    - Television, Boxing, 1948 July-Nov.
    - Fights, 1948 June-Sept.
    - Yankee Football, 1948 Aug.-Dec.
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Spot announcements, 1948 July 16
      [In Spanish, for Puerto Rico and Venezuela]
    - Kraft Music Hall, Al Jolson, 1948 Jan.-June (Reel 423)
    - Kraft Music Hall, Al Jolson, 1948 June, Sept.-Dec. (Reel 424)
    - Summer show, Nelson Eddy, 1948 June-Sept.
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1948 Jan.-Apr.
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1948 Apr.-Aug. (Reel 425)
      [No broadcasts June 23, July 14 due to political conventions]
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1948 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 426)
      [See reel 427 for Dec. 15]
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1948 Dec. (Reel 427)
  - Ford Motor Company
    - Recorded spot, 1948 Mar. 8
      [See reel 419 for more]
  - Libby, McNeil & Libby (Reel 445)
    - My True Story, monitor reports, 1945
    - My True Story, commercials, 1945
    - My True Story, 1945 Nov.-Dec. (Reel 446)
    - My True Story, commercials, 1945 Nov.-Dec.
    - My True Story, commercials, 1946 May
    - My True Story, monitor reports, 1946
    - My True Story, 1947 Dec.-1948 Mar.
    - My True Story, 1948 Mar.-Aug. (Reel 447)
    - My True Story, 1948 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 448)
  - Lever Brothers
    - The Clock, scripts, 1949 Oct.
    - The Clock, scripts, 1949 Oct.-1950 Mar. (Reel 449)
  - Libby, McNeil & Libby
    - My True Story, 1949 Jan.-Feb.
    - My True Story, 1949 Mar.-Aug. (Reel 528)
    - My True Story, 1949 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 529)
    - Mr. Christoph's comments on synopsis, 1949 Jan.-Aug.
    - Mr. Christoph's comments on synopsis, 1949 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 530)
    - Monitor reports, 1949
    - My True Story, scripts, 1950 Jan.-Aug.
    - Monitor reports, 1950
    - Mr. Christoph's comments on synopsis, 1950 Jan.-Apr.
    - My True Story, magazine outlines, 1949-1950 (Reel 531)
  - Mentholatum, Mentholatum Mountaineers, auditions, spots, 1944-1945 (Reel 717)
  - Standard Brands
    - Robert Shaw Chorale, 1948 June-Aug.
  - Scott Paper/Wine Advisory Board
    - Diane Lucas Cooking show, 1949 Feb.-Dec.
  - Ward Baking
    - Aunt Hannah's Kiddie Show, 1948 Jan.-1949 Apr.
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    - Music America Loves Best, 1949 Jan.-Apr.
    - Hile Damroth commercials, 1949
  - Ford Dealers of America
    - Spot announcements, 1949 Jan.
  - Kraft Cheese
    - International, 1949 Jan.
  - Rayve Home Permanent
    - Winner Take All, auditions, 1949 Jan.
  - P. Ballantine & Sons
    - TV Film commercials, 1949 Feb.-June
    - With General Cigar, Exhibition Games, 1948 Aug. 18
    - N.Y. Yankees vs. Giants, 1949 June. 27
  - Oren Root
    - Campaign Issues, 1949 Oct.-Nov.
  - Ford Dealers of America
    - Dickens' Christmas Carol, 1949 Dec. 24-25
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    - Transcriptions,1950
    - Screen Directors Playhouse, 1950 Jan.-June
      [No script for Jan. 13]
    - Screen Directors Playhouse, 1950 June 30 (Reel 718)
  - Penick & Ford
    - Br'er Rabbit, commercials, 1949
  - Textron
    - Textron Theatre, The Hartmans, 1949 Feb.-May
  - J.B. Williams
    - Act II, 1949 Mar.-July
    - Say It With Acting, 1949 Aug.-Oct.
    - Say It With Acting, 1949 Oct.-1950 Aug. (Reel 719)
      [No script for July 30]
  - General Cigar (White Owl)
    - Yankees baseball, 1949-1950
  - P. Ballantine & Sons (Reel 720)
    - Boxing, 1949 Jan.-1950 Feb.
    - Baseball, rained out games, 1949 May 22, July 10
    - Yankees Baseball, radio, 1949-1950
    - Yankees Baseball, television, 1949-1950
    - Yankees Baseball, simultaneous radio and television, 1949-1950 (Reel 721)
    - Believe It Or Not, 1950 Jan.-June
      [To Part II, page 14 of June 1]
    - Believe It Or Not, 1950 June-Sept. (Reel 722)
      [From Part II, page 15 of June 1]
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Music Hall, 1949 Jan.-May
    - Kraft Summer Show, 1949 Summer
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1949 Jan.-Feb. 9
      [Part of Feb. 9]
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1949 Feb.-June 22 (Reel 723)
      [Rest of Feb. 9; May 18 missing; part of June 22, Pink String and Sealing Wax]
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1949 June 22-Sept 28 (Reel 724)
      [Rest of June 22, Pink String and Sealing Wax; part of Sept. 28, Climax'
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1949 Sept. 28-1950 Feb. 8 (Reel 725)
      [Rest of Sept. 28, Climax; Feb. 8 to end of Act II]
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1950 Feb. 8-June 14 (Reel 726)
      [Feb. 8 Act III, The Dark Towers]
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1950 June 21-Oct. 11 (Reel 729)
      [Part of Oct. 11, The Great Broxopp; see also reel 737]
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1950 Oct. 11 (Reel 730)
      [End of Oct. 11, The Great Broxopp]
    - The Falcon, 1950
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Radio Theatre, Aunt Jenny Hitchhikes, 1949 Jan.-Apr.
    - Lux Radio Theatre, The Mating of Millie, 1949 Jan. 3
      [Acts I, II]
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1949 (Reel 731)
      [End of Jan. 3, The Mating of Millie; Dec. 26 to end of Act I]
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1949 Dec. 26-1950 Oct. 30 (Reel 732)
      [End of Dec. 26; Oct. 30 to end of Act II]
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1950 Oct. 30 (Reel 733)
      [End of broadcast]
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1950 Oct.-Dec.
  - Standard Brands
    - One Man's Family, 1949 Jan.-Apr.
    - Fleischmann's Yeast, One Man's Family, commercials, 1949
  - Johns-Manville (Reel 734)
    - Bill Henry News, 1949 Oct.-Dec.
  - Ford Dealers of America
    - Through the Crystal Ball, 1949 Apr.-June
    - Spot announcements, 1949
    - Variety Show, 1949 June-July
    - Fred Allen Show, 1949 Jan.-June
    - College of Musical Knowledge, 1949 Dec.-1950 Nov. (Reel 735)
      [Part of Nov. 30]
    - College of Musical Knowledge, 1950 Nov.-30-Dec. (Reel 736)
      [Rest of Nov. 30]
    - Saturday News, 1950 Dec.
    - Dr. Marshall, 1950 Nov.-Dec.
  - Pan American World Airways
    - Nights in Latin America, 1950 Apr.-Dec.
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    - Show of Shows, commercials, 1950 Mar.-May
  - Fannie Farmer Candies
    - Buffalo Billy Show, 1950 Oct.-Dec.
  - Rayve Home Permanent
    - Junior Miss, 1950 Jan.-Sept.
    - Junior Miss, 1950 Sept.-Dec. (Reel 737)
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1950 Oct. 11
      [Pages 13-21 of Act II, The Great Broxopp]
  - Standard Brands
    - One Man's Family, radio histories, 1932-1949
    - Bergen Shaw, Open Door, radio histories, coffee spots, 1928-1949
    - Fred Allen Show, radio histories, 1945-1947
    - Mary Martin, radio histories, 1943-1945
    - Hour Glass, Face to Face, television histories, 1946-1949
    - Fleischmann Yeast, 1945-1946
  - P. Ballantine & Sons (Reel 788)
    - Yankees Baseball, television, 1951 July-Sept.
    - Yankees Baseball, simulcast, 1951 Apr.-Sept.
  - Fannie Farmer Candies
    - Buffalo Billy Show, no scripts, 1951 Jan. 7, 14
  - Ford Motor Company
    - Ford Star Theater, scripts, 1951 Jan.-Mar.
  - Johns-Manville
    - News, scripts, 1951 Jan.-Mar.
    - News, scripts, 1951 Mar.-Dec. (Reel 789)
    - Fair Meadows USA, 1951 Nov.-Dec.
  - Kraft Cheese
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1951 Jan.-Feb 28
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1951 Feb. 28-June 27 (Reel 790)
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1951 June 27-Nov. 7 (Reel 791)
    - Kraft Television Theatre, 1951 Nov. 7-Dec. (Reel 792)
    - Bobby Benson Show, 1951 Jan.
    - The Falcon, 1951 Jan.-Aug. 22
    - The Falcon, 1951 Aug. 22-30 (Reel 793)
  - Lever Brothers
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1951 Jan.-Nov. 12
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1951 Nov. 12-Dec. (Reel 794)
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1951 Jan.-Sept. 10
    - Lux Video Theatre, 1951 Sept. 10-Dec. (Reel 795)
  - Pan American World Airways
    - Nights in Latin America, 1951 Jan.-June
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    - With U.S. Steel, Theater Guild On The Air, Hamlet, 1951
    - Phil Harris/Alice Faye Show, 1951 Mar.-May, Sept.-Dec.
    - Muscial Merry-Go-Round, 1951 May-June
    - Rex Saunders, 1951 May-June
    - Lifeline (Blood Bank show), 1951 Oct. 26
    - Ezio Pinza Show, 1951 Nov.-Dec.
  - Swift & Co.
    - Swift's Movie Time, 1951 Oct.-Nov. 2
    - Swift's Movie Time, 1951 Nov. 2-Dec. (Reel 796)
  - Kraft Cheese (Reel 905)
    - Kraft Television Theatre
      - The New Gossoon, 1952 Jan. 2
      - Philip Goes Forth, 1952 Jan. 9
      - The Round Table, 1952 Jan. 16
      - The Peaceful Warrior, 1952 Jan. 23
      - Mrs. O'Brien Entertains, 1952 Jan. 30
      - Mrs. O'Brien Entertains, (continued), 1952 Jan. 30 (Reel 906)
      - Follow the Dream, 1952 Feb. 6
      - The Skin Game, 1952 Feb. 13
      - The Mollusc, 1952 Feb. 20
      - September Tide, 1952 Mar.27
      - What Anne Brought Home, 1952 Mar. 5
      - The Thief, 1952 Mar. 12
      - The Bride the Sun Shines On, 1952 Mar. 19
      - The Rugged Path, 1952 Mar. 26
        [Missing]
      - The Ryan Girl, 1952 Apr. 2
      - The Last Mile, 1952 Apr. 9
      - Green Cars Go East, 1952 Apr. 16
      - The Summit, 1952 Apr. 23
      - The Man in Half Moon Street, 1952 Apr. 30
      - She Stoops to Conquer, 1952 May 7
      - The Inn, 1952 May 14
      - Prologue to Glory, 1952 May 21
      - The Third Visitor, 1952 May 28
      - The Third Visitor, (continued), 1952 May 28 (Reel 907)
      - At Mrs. Beam's, 1952 June 4
      - Cricket on the Hearth, 1952 June 11
      - Death of Kid Slawson, 1952 June 18
      - Joy for Mourning, 1952 June 25
      - Time for Turning, 1952 July 2
      - The Great Big Doorstep, 1952 July 16
      - The Music Master, 1952 July 30
      - Six By Six, 1952 Aug. 6
      - Lace on Her Petticoat, 1952 Aug. 13
      - Indian Summer, 1952 Aug. 20
      - The Small Hours, 1952 Aug. 27
      - Mr. Barry's Etchings, 1952 Sept. 3
      - Letters to Lucerne, 1952 Sept. 10
      - The Grass Harp, 1952 Sept. 17
      - Background, 1952 Sept. 24
      - Michael & Mary, 1952 Oct. 1
      - The New Tenant, 1952 Oct. 8
      - The New Tenant, (continued), 1952 Oct. 8 (Reel 908)
      - A Kiss for Cinderella, 1952 Oct. 15
      - A Long Night in Forty Mile, 1952 Oct. 22
      - The Divine Drudge, 1952 Oct. 29
      - Melody Jones, 1952 Nov. 5
      - Hilda McKay, 1952 Nov. 12
      - Quiet Wedding, 1952 Nov. 19
      - Mr. Lazarus, 1952 Nov. 26
      - The Empty House, 1952 Dec. 3
      - Intimate Strangers, 1952 Dec. 10
      - The Guest Room, 1952 Dec. 17
      - A Christmas Carol, 1952 Dec. 24
      - Paper Moon, 1952 Dec. 31
  - P. Ballantine & Sons
    - Yankees Baseball
      - Radio, 1952 Mar.-Apr. 30